It's all up to you, everyone.
Come here.
How many servings, sweetie?
I'd like to have a serving.
One serving, huh? Gosh!
Why only one serving?
I'd like one bowl of rice noodle soup.
Other customers can come here to support the owner.
The owner may get more support from other people, right?
Alright, one serving for this little girl.
Which grade are you in?
I'm in the first grade.
You're the same age as Tu.
Thank you, sweetie.
Why so much, girl?
You paid VND100,000 for this bowl, huh?
Thanks a ton.
Hey, Thanh.
VND300,000 for the first serving.
Okay.
I'd like 2 servings, please.
- 2 servings, huh?
- Yes, please.
Okay.
VND60,000 for 2 servings.
Two servings, please!
Here are your servings.
Thanks a lot for supporting us.
Hello, sis.
May I have 10 servings?
Ten servings.
Oh, whoa! 10 servings!
Excuse me, sis.
We've prepared just 150 servings today.
Lots of people are still waiting to support Thanh.
Would you mind buying fewer servings?
That's okay.
- How many servings would you like to buy?
- Just 5, please.
Okay, I appreciate it much.
Make sure that you give her 5 servings.
Five servings for you.
We're preparing a bag of broth. Just give us a sec.
How much in total?
The owner sells it at VND20,000/bowl
but today you can give him as much as you want.
- VND100,000, right?
- That's it.
Oh, she's given me VND400,000.
Thanks a bunch.
- Thanks, sis.
- May I take a photo with you?
- I have 2 servings, please.
- Okay, thanks.
VND40,000 for 2 servings.
How can you know that I'm here?
By watching your live stream.
Oh, thank you a lot.
I have 2 servings.
A foreign sponsor donates VND500,000
to the character of the show today.
- Here's your VND500,000.
- Yeah.
2 servings, please.
VND500,000 from a foreign sponsor.
VND800,000 for 2 servings.
VND400,000 for each.
That's a new record, everyone.
[VND400,000 for a bowl of rice noodle soup]
Come here, please.
- This is for him. No need to give me the food.
- Really?
[Have you got surprised?]
VND200,000 for no food.
Sounds a bit weird.
I appreciate it.
Thanks.
She wanna give a chance to other customers.
It's very kind of her.
- A serving at VND100,000, please.
- Thanks a ton.
VND100,000 for this serving.
One serving, please!
- I'm a huge fan of yours, Color Man.
- Thank you very much.
One more serving.
Alright, here you are!
- Two servings, please!
- Thanks.
Just buy one or two servings, everyone.
Try to make this challenge harder.
The food will be easily sold out
if you buy a few servings at once.
Make it harder.
If you fail it, I'll donate more money to him.
- Thanks for your support.
- Welcome.
Dear, everyone.
The challenge is to sell 150 servings.
If you come to support us,
please don't buy too many servings at once.
Just one or two servings.
Make the challenge more difficult
and let more customers support Thanh and Minh Tu.
If I fail to sell 150 bowls
of rice noodle soup within 90 minutes,
I have to give him VND10 million.
You know, I wanna fail this challenge.
So just come to buy one or two servings.
Come here, boy.
A serving at VND200,000 for this little boy.
- Which grade are you in?
- I'm in the fifth grade.
Thank you very much.
You look more handsome than on the TV.
Thanks a lot.
- Five servings, please.
- Give us a minute.
- You've just checked out my eatery.
- Is that so?
Com Nha 1989 eatery.
Ah, I remember.
It's such a great rice eatery.
VND500,000 for 5 servings.
Thanks very much.
Here you are.
- Do you know Com Nha 1989 eatery?
- Check it out again if you have time.
Thanks for your support. Bye for now!
One serving for you.
Such an adorable kid!
VND20,000 for one serving.
Thanks a lot.
- Two more customers.
- VND200,000 for 2 servings.
And one serving at VND50,000 for this lady.
Three servings in total.
Two servings, huh?
Hey, everyone.
Well, I...
One customer can buy only one serving.
You can't catch up, huh?
[Working non-stop]
What now? I'm a bit overwhelmed now.
[Lots of customers are waiting]
Can't catch up, huh?
Can you sing or do something to buy the time?
Dear, everyone! One customer can only buy one serving.
We can't catch up with your orders.
- One serving, please.
- Got it.
We'd better take some photos to buy the time.
- I'm a big fan of your.
- Thanks, sis.
No one eats at our place, huh?
Come here, little boy.
It's all up to you to decide the price.
Thanks for your support.
The organizers only allow me to sell one customer a serving.
My Goodness!
That's challenging!
They wanna make it harder!
Come here, sis.
You can stay here and enjoy rice noodle soup.
VND100,000 for 5 servings.
Give me a minute, please.
One serving at VND20,000.
- Excuse me?
- One serving costs VND20,000, right?
We're just allowed to sell one serving for a customer.
- I wanna buy 2 servings for my children.
- That's okay.
- How many servings?
- Five, please.
- Five, right?
- My great-grandma wanna support you.
Oh, really?
Wait for a second, sis.
Her change is VND400,000.
Gosh, why does it take so long?
Let me give him a hand.
[Are you sure?]
May I enjoy one bowl right here?
Just one serving for each customer.
We can't catch up with the orders.
One customer one serving!
The challenge is harder for me to overcome.
Thanks.
One serving at VND100,000.
Thanks very much, sis.
Dear, beloved viewers.
We didn't expect things would go like this.
Now just play it by ear.
Our crew visited Quang Trung Museum this morning.
I went to Dai Kinh Thien in Tay Son,
where the locals annually make the offerings to King Quang Trung.
It might bring us lots of good luck.
So many customers come here to support us.
- Hello, uncle.
- Hi.
I have 2 servings.
- Would you mind getting just one?
- Okay.
Come here.
- Two servings, please.
- One for me, the other for my mom.
Alright, accepted.
- One for your mom.
- Thanks.
Two servings.
One customer, one serving.
How about two?
[What do you mean?]
- Alright.
- Give me some slices of lime, please.
Okay, just a second.
- I have one bowl, please.
- That's nice! Just one customer, one serving.
Make the challenge harder.
Your food has been sold out, hasn't it?
How many servings are left?
How many bowls?
- How many?
- 30 bowls, huh?
- More than 30 servings.
- Around 40.
Make it quick!
[Hang in there, Thanh]
You've just sold 73 servings, huh?
Ladies and gentlemen,
we've just finished 73 servings.
[73 servings in 45 minutes]
77 servings to go!
It's just 5:50 pm now.
Hope that I can accomplish the challenge in 60 minutes.
Please give us some minutes, everyone.
- I have one serving.
- Okay, good boy.
Here you are.
One for this man, please.
- Keep the change for the owners.
- Oh, thanks a lot.
One serving at VND40,000.
One more, please.
Yeah.
VND150,000 for 6 servings, please.
Just 2 servings per customer are the maximum.
Alright, 2 servings.
She wanna buy 6 servings but couldn't make it.
[The number of the servings: 97]
Please try to understand.
Thank you a lot.
- How about you?
- 2 servings, please.
Two servings, huh?
Dear, everyone! His rice noodle soup doesn't have a fixed price today.
I have two, please.
How adorable! VND100,000 for 2 servings.
Thanks a ton.
One more, please.
The prices of almost all the servings are doubled.
Thanks, sis.
Where's your phone?
My husband is holding it.
Oh, her husband.
One customer buys one serving.
So that more people can come here to support us.
Alright.
One serving for you.
Why a lot, sis? Please go out this way.
Thanks a ton.
VND50,000 for this serving.
Thanks for your support, everyone.
Just one serving per customer is maximum.
[What are you looking for?]
- Out of rice noodles, huh?
- There's still some left.
[We're preparing it]
- I just give him VND100,000. No food is needed.
- Thanks.
She donated VND100,000 to the owners.
Ladies and gentlemen, we've already sold 110 servings.
Forty servings left to go!
One customer, one serving!
40 servings left!
- Come here, please.
- May I take a photo with you.
Here's the money. No food is needed.
Oh, they even don't want the food.
Thanks a ton.
Glad that we can save more food.
- How much broth do we have left?
- A lot.
[Don't worry]
Isn't it a pot of broth?
- Or just boiling water?
- It's for parboiling the rice noodles.
We've still got much broth
but gonna run out of other ingredients.
I see.
The ingredients are just enough for 150 bowls.
That's the fastest he could do.
- Two bowls, please.
- Okay.
One customer, one serving, please!
One, please!
Just one serving for each customer.
You wanna sit here, right?
Two servings for us, please.
We'd like to enjoy the food here.
That's okay.
- Sit here, right?
- Yes.
Two bowls of rice noodle soup, please.
One more serving, please.
Only one bowl per customer.
We're gonna sell out the rice noodle soup.
- I'd like one serving, please.
- Okay.
How about 2 assorted servings?
One customer can buy one serving.
We're almost out of the food.
Please try to understand.
You can come here tomorrow.
Thanks, little boy.
I'd like to donate this amount of money to the show.
He buys a serving at VND1 million! Oh, wow!
Wish you health and happiness.
Gosh, we've just broken a new record.
A serving at VND1 million.
Hata Hotel in Quy Nhon donates VND1 million to the show.
I appreciate it, uncle.
An old man from the Hata hotel in Quy Nhon
bought a bowl at VN1 million.
We've got 2 servings at VND1 million/each.
Thanks for your support.
Awesome!
Thanks, girl. Go out this way.
My bad! I almost forgot!
I'm a bit overwhelmed.
- I wanna send him some money.
- Thanks.
She's donating money to him.
No food needed.
One customer, one serving, please!
The elderly should be given priority.
Each customer can buy only one serving.
We're almost out of the food.
One bowl, right?
Move here, girls.
- And one for you, huh?
- Yes.
One bowl of you two, right?
How adorable!
Here you are.
Oh, lords!
This is your savings, right?
[You know it all]
One customer, one serving, please!
Thanks a lot.
We're gonna run out of food.
Can you buy just one bowl?
[I agree]
All for one serving, huh?
We've just got more than 10 servings left.
Please try to understand, everyone!
Thanks, little girl.
Move here to take a photo with me, sweetie.
We've got only 5 bowls left.
Dear, everyone.
There are only 5 servings left.
Please try to understand.
One serving.
Another one, please.
Three servings left.
The last 3 bowls.
One for you.
You can come here to take a photo with me, everyone.
Thanks for supporting us.
Two more left.
One for you, right? Alright, thanks a bunch.
It's the last serving.
A sponsor from Switzerland
wanna send this to the owners.
Oh, thanks.
One serving at VND50,000 for this woman.
A sponsor from Switzerland sent us VND1 million.