- So they let you sit here?
- Yes.
No fees at all? That's great.
It used to be spacious and I could place a stall here.
What do you think of filming an episode of Street Cry here?
It may be overcrowded. Yes?
I'm making a show called Street Cry 4.0.
- It's ok. Mrs. Hang is easy-going.
- I'm afraid the crowd would cause inconvenience.
Mrs. Hang won't mind. She is very nice.
Mrs. Hang is the owner of
the plastic store right next to us.
Well, there may not be enough space here.
It's more spacious when the surrounding stalls close.
Usually, there are other stalls around me.
So, it'd be better to film in the afternoon, right?
Sure.
I think Granny Dan is famous in Phan Thiet, isn't she?
- Of course.
- Many people in the market tell me about her.
Everyone knows about her and her difficult life.
- That's why they usually offer her food.
- I see.
Thanks to the philanthropists that
I don't have to starve. Look at the noodles and milk!
You can sell up to 160 servings per day?
They adore her and often help her get more food.
Mrs. Hang usually stands up for me
when I get treated unfairly.
I use the donated food efficiently.
Is it true that your legs are hurt?
I have bow legs so I can't walk.
- Really?
- I can only move around by holding onto something.
Yeah, I have to sit on a cart and
ask her to push me here.
- You can't walk at all?
- Yeah.
I can make 1 or 2 steps.
- Which leg?
- They curve outwards at the knees.
- Oh, both of your legs are bowed out so you can't move.
- Yes.
The bow legs make me unable to walk properly.
I sit on her cart and she would give me a ride.
- How do you move around at home?
- I can hold onto the wall and the furniture.
Who makes the sweet soup?
- Me.
- Oh, I see.
Granny offers 3 types of sweet soup.
The business is not very good these days
though I only offer 3 types.
This is Dau Xanh Danh (Mashed Mung Bean Sweet Soup).
- All goes at VND5,000 per serving?
- Yes.
Oh gosh, how much profit do you make
per serving? Like VND1,000?
No way.
OMG! VND5,000 per serving is too cheap.
- The profit per serving is only a few hundred VND.
- Not even VND1,000?
Many people tell me to increase the price to
VND6,000 - 7,000 per serving but I don't want to.
- You should. The cost of living keeps rising up these days.
- Yeah, but I don't have many customers.
I usually receive rice from the philanthropists.
I only have to earn money to buy medicines
and some food like fish.
I can get about VND100,000 if sold out.
I guess your maximum daily profit is VND100,000, right?
- Yes.
- Around that.
If the business is good, I can make up to VND120,000.
Otherwise, I make no profit.
But you never think of quitting?
- I can't stand staying at home and doing nothing.
- Let your kids take care of you.
- Or count on the neighbors.
- Yeah, but I can't stand it.
Working makes me feel happier.
Her children don't support her financially.
- I see.
- They would provide her some food though.
But many people are supporting you, right?
- Yes. I've received lots of rice and stuff.
- I see. You just love doing your job.
Sure. I'll work until I can't anymore.
I'll keep doing my job as long as I'm able to.
It was torture to stay at home during the pandemic.
I don't mind if the sales are slow.
It's still better than being stuck at home.
Maybe I'm used to being busy with work.
- Yeah, she's been selling sweet soup for almost half a century.
- Nah, more than 40 years.
- When you were 30 years old?
- No, I was only 27 when I started.
I see.
What did you do before selling sweet soup?
I sold iced tea at home.
I also offered noodles and congee.
I sold all kinds of things.
You know, I did everything I can.
I sold iced tea in my neighborhood,
at my house. I could do everything.
You know, I didn't mind anything.
I've been selling sweet soup here for more than 40 years.
I decided to stick with it.
I feel sorry for her.
Still, she's determined to earn money on her own.