Please get me some bowls to try.
Let's move there, it's larger.
I'm good, I can sit here.
- It's a bit narrow.
- No worries.
Do you know me?
- No, I don't.
- It's okay.
Yeah, let me tell you.
Maybe after 7 or 10 days, I'll come back here.
To film an episode for my series named Street Cry.
Street Cry 4.0.
Normally, I will help the people in need,
who make ends meet themselves.
I will help with your selling for one day.
I'll try to help you sell about 150 bowls.
If we can't reach that target, I will buy them all.
- It would be so hard for you and your team.
- Never mind.
Don't worry, it doesn't matter.
Now I'm waiting for my noodles.
[Hi everyone, I'm Tu]
Get me some dry noodles.
Prepare yourself. Selling 150 bowls of noodles is not easy.
- It's not easy, is it?
- Try to prepare enough ingredients.
Tasty-looking.
It looks really good.
Are your father's noodles delicious?
Is it good?
- Good or not?
- Yes, yes.
[How can I say it's bad?]
It's good, isn't it?
- Do you usually eat?
- Yes.
[I'm his loyal customer.]
- Really? Do you eat it every day?
- Once two days.
As the main course?
You're already in grade 1, try to get good results.
I haven't yet. I'm still in kindergarten.
So that means you're not 6.
No.
- I'm already 6.
- No way.
Here. A bowl of dry noodles.
Alright.
Chopsticks and spoons are already here.
Let's try the broth.
Thank you.
What a delicious rib.
Wow, you're so polite.
Do you also help your father?
[I'm the boss here]
Oh, the bottle lid just falls.
The rib is so fresh.
A bowl of noodles with ribs is only VND20,000 or VND25,000.
[Let's turn to our dry noodles.]
This is definitely "Mi go" style.
This shacha sauce is the signature.
[It looks so spicy.]
Sure.
It must go with this sauce.
[The food "torture" starts here.]
It tastes really good.
Once again, thank all the audience for introducing me.
[1 day ago]
Ladies and gentlemen. I've reached the center of Quy Nhon city.
And this is a park near Quan Tran market.
I guess that you still remember the cart over there where Mr Tu and his daughter sell noodles.
Here is also the place for filming an episode of Street Cry...
to help Mr Thanh and Minh Tu, right here at this park, near Quan Tran market.
Don't forget to come.
And now I'm about to visit his home.
[Let's visit his home]
This is the alley leading to his home.
It's too narrow.
It's about only 1 meter.
I can't even fully stretch my arm.
Where's his house?
Above this ladder?
Dear audiences, this is the ladder leading to his home.
You can see, it's nearly broken.
Really bad condition.
It's so dangerous if more than one person climbs over.
[Only for one person]
Oh god.
[Not safe]
I'm so worried. I weigh more than 75 kilos.
I can feel it shaking.
[Try to keep calm]
I'm so scared.
[But it's still scary]
The kid's sandals. So lovely.
[Neatly arranged]
- Hi.
- Hello, uncle.
[So obedient]
Do you still remember me?
Yes.
What? Still remember me?
Are you two having lunch?
- She needs to eat early.
- I see you're having pork organ congee for lunch.
How large is this room?
It's less than 11 square meters.
[It's too small]
Less than 11 square meters.
- That's the picture of your wife?
- Yes, that's her.
- Nguyen Thi Thu Hien?
- Yes.
Born on October 25, 1977.
That means she's one year smaller than you.
Her hometown is Thuy Thach village, Pho Cuong commune,
Duc Pho district, Quang Ngai province.
It's your hometown, too?
Did you draw it?
- Do you have any photos of her?
- Yes.
I just get them retouched and put them in the wardrobe.
- Mostly my wedding photos.
- Where is the altar?
In my hometown.
I've changed my places a lot so I don't dare to put it here.
This baby girl, what do you like?
I like "but mau" (crayons) only.
What is "mut mau" (misheard)
That's the crayons used for coloring things.
Ah, "but mau".
I misheard that word.
I had no idea what is "mut mau".
Anything else?
I like crabs and shrimps.
Crabs and shrimps?
You like seafood, don't you?
[You make me want to eat them, too]
Do you eat them regularly?
Yes, I do.
When I was at my grandma's house, Dad always cooked for me.
[My dad is no.1]
Dad always cooked for you.
Tomorrow, I'll try to help your dad to get more money.
And then we'll buy you what you like.
What is your dream?
I want to be a cook.
And we will also buy you a set of cooking toys, okay?
- Is it okay?
- Yes, it is.
Do you want anything else?
Look at your teeth. They look so funny.
[You keep teasing me]
Okay now I'm supposed to take you to the market
and buy you crayons, right?
- There aren't any crayons in the market.
- I think there are.
- To sum up, we need to buy crayons and a set of toys.
- Yes.
Do you want some new dresses?
No, I'm good. I have many at home.
[My Dad bought enough for me]
She's so lovely and obedient.
- Hello everyone.
- Hello all the audience.
Dear audiences, I'm at Tang Bat Ho street. My team has found a toy store.
What do you like?
You'll get what you like.
What is this?
A beauty playset.
But you said you like cooking toys.
Ok, whatever. Just take what you like.
Bring them here and I'll buy them for you.
Alright.
Now you can choose cooking toys and then we'll find the crayons.
Which one do you like?
[A set of cooking toys]
Oh, wow.
You like this one?
Uish.
[You need to compensate]
It's broken.
- Do you like this one? Anything else?
- She likes this one.
Okay now.
Why is it so heavy?
Is it heavy? Hold them in that way.
Can you?
- Okay now take them to the car. We'll go to buy crayons.
- Okay, uncle.
Let me pay.
Did you buy it?
Ms My already bought it.
Ms My bought it for you.
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
This is my favorite crayon set.
- Which one?
- Here it is.
The one with a Doraemon image?
[I'm so satisfied]
Oh, wow.
What will you color? There are some color books.
Open them.
I'll open this one.
Wow.
You will follow this to color.
Let's get in the car.
When you grow up, if you're successful
with your own business, don't forget me.
Yes.
[Please wait for me]
You say yes but you will forget, won't you?
Will you forget?
How can you recognize me if I'm older?
[No way]
Look at my face.
Remember it?
Remember.
Don't forget to find me 10 years after.
[The time has come]
Dear audiences, I, Mr Thanh and
Minh Tu are at a park near Quan Tran market.
Located near the junction of Tang Bat Ho and
Tran Nguyen Dan street of Quy Nhon city.
Usually, this cart will be put over there.
But today, we sincerely thank the authorities
for supporting me as well as the Street Cry 4.0 series.
It's so large and there's enough space for people to come.
Although we have 5 minutes left to start, it's so crowded here.
Actually, I was quite worried about the weather.
But fortunately, everything's still fine until now.
Today I hope that we will reach our target:
sell out 150 bowls of noodles.
Are you happy? You dress so well today.
Dear audiences, this is Minh Tu, 6 years old.
Let's get started.
Today we've got 90 minutes. Can we sell out 150 bowls?
This all depends on you, the audience.
- They're all packed and ready? How many of them?
- 40.
We're having 40 available bowls.
Dear everyone, usually he sells with the price from VND15,000-20,000 with a small rib.
But today you can freely give the price.
Up to you and your conscience.